<resources>
    <string name="app_name">DietBalanceApplication</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Diet Balance</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">aaradietcare@adc.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="menu_home">Home</string>
    <string name="menu_gallery">Gallery</string>
    <string name="menu_slideshow">Slideshow</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="dietFragmentName">Diet Balance</string>
    <string name="fragment_user_profile">User Profile</string>
    <string name="fragment_calculator">Calorie Calculator</string>
    <string name="fragment_recipe">Sample Healthy Recipes</string>
    <string name="fragment_diet_tips">Diet Tips</string>
    <string name="fragment_bog">Blogs</string>
    <string name="fragment_more_info">More Information</string>


    <string name="avocado">Avocado Sandwich</string>
    <string name="avocadoDesc">\t\t\tThis is a good option for lunch or dinner. It does not use too much cheese, and avocados contain healthy fats and nutrients </string>
    <string name="avocado_ing">\t\t\tYou will only need one ripe tomato, one avocado, sliced bread, butter, mozzarella cheese slices and a sprinkle of salt. </string>
    <string name="eggs">Scrambled Eggs</string>
    <string name="eggDesc">\t\t\tEggs are a good source of protein. Eggs taste good, are protein-filled and really easy to make. </string>
    <string name="egg_ing">\t\t\tYou will only need a mixing bowl, eggs, goat cheese, salt, fresh-ground black pepper, butter and chopped chives. </string>
    <string name="salad">Salad</string>
    <string name="saladDesc">\t\t\t Sprucing up your leafy greens with veggies, beans, chickpeas, nuts or seeds, and then drizzling with olive oil and vinegar. You can add a piece of crispy bread to make it more of a meal. </string>
    <string name="salad_ing">\t\t\t If you eat meat, add chicken or tuna. For extra flavor, consider a sprinkle of salt.  </string>
    <string name="omelet">Cheese Omelet</string>
    <string name="omeletDesc">\t\t\tThis is a good option for lunch or dinner.You can add a fried egg on top of anything and make it more of a hearty meal, like on top of salad</string>
    <string name="omelet_ing">\t\t\t You need parsley, garlic cloves, olive oil, red wine vinegar, salt and red pepper flakes. You can also add steak, fish, taco or sandwich dishes. </string>
    <string name="quesadillas">Greek Quesadillas</string>
    <string name="quesadillasDesc">\t\t\tThe Greek quesadillas are packed with vegetables such as spinach and peppers. It is just a good way to make a satisfying meal that is easy to make. </string>
    <string name="quesadillas_ing">\t\t\tYou will need tortillas, fresh spinach, red onion, roasted red peppers, black olives, shredded mozzarella cheese, feta cheese crumbles, oregano and/or red pepper flakes.  </string>
    <string name="veggie">Veggie Sandwich</string>
    <string name="veggieDesc">\t\t\tThis sandwich is made with hummus – and it is vegan-friendly. Combine whatever vegetables you have on hand with hummus on a sandwich. It is delicious and satisfying, and it is good for you. </string>
    <string name="veggie_ing">\t\t\tYou will only need  a red onion, one carrot, pea shoots, whole-grain bread and feta cheese crumbles. </string>
    <string name="DieticianNearby">Dietician Nearby</string>
    <string name="DieticianEmail">Email Us</string>
    <string name="DieticianPhone">Phone</string>
    <string name="DieticianMessage">SMS at</string>
    <string name="DieticianSocial">Social Media</string>
    <string name="faqTitle">Frequently Asked Question</string>
    <string name="faqMenu">FAQ</string>
    <string name="aboutDiet">It is an application that helps users with various dietary plans. This app will help the users maintain a healthy diet. This will helps users to follow proper diet and keep count on their calorie’s intake. This will help users to lose weight, stay healthy and stronger.</string>
    <string name="dietDesc">\t\tEating a healthy, balanced diet is one of the most important things you can do to protect your health. It is not about strict limitations, staying unrealistically thin, or depriving yourself of the foods you love. Rather, it’s about feeling great, having more energy, improving your health, and boosting your mood.Healthy lifestyle is gaining popularity day by day in this modern times.</string>

    <string name="bmiButtonText">Body Mass Index</string>
    <string name="calorieButton">Calorie Calculator</string>
    <string name="pregnancyCalculator">Pregnancy Calorie Calculator</string>
    <string name="feedingCalculator">BreastFeeding Calorie Calculator</string>
    <string name="weightButton">Ideal Weight</string>
    <!-- Preference Titles -->
    <string name="messages_header">Messages</string>
    <string name="sync_header">Sync</string>

    <!-- Messages Preferences -->
    <string name="signature_title">Your signature</string>
    <string name="reply_title">Default reply action</string>

    <!-- Sync Preferences -->
    <string name="sync_title">Sync email periodically</string>
    <string name="attachment_title">Download incoming attachments</string>
    <string name="attachment_summary_on">Automatically download attachments for incoming emails
    </string>
    <string name="attachment_summary_off">Only download attachments when manually requested</string>

</resources>